As your code base grows, you may find yourself needing to re-evaluate what
在代码量增长的过程中 你可能需要
information is essential for your documentation.
重新评估哪些信息应包含到文档中
Deciding what goes into your readme is entirely up to you.
在 readme 中加入什么是完全由你决定的
But let's go over a few common sections and then use cases in a readme.
我们先来看看 readme 的常见部分及若干用例
Including copyright or licensing information, or at least a link to it,
引入版权或者证书信息 又或至少加入一条链接
is always a good idea, no matter how large or small a project.
这对项目很有益处
By default, you retain full rights to your code even if you don't
默认情况下你对相应代码保留所有权利
include a license, but it's a safer bet to be explicit about this.
但还是加入证书信息 多一份保障好些
Often, what you really want to do though,
通常你会希望
is allow others to contribute to your project.
他人可以向你的项目贡献代码
In this case, it's super important to include a license.
这时你一定要声明证书信息
You can choose to include the full license in your readme itself,
你可以把它直接写到 readme 里
or you can link out to it from your readme.
也可以在 readme 放置一条指向它的链接
Choosing which license is a bit beyond the scope of this course, but
具体证书的选择超出了本课程的范围
I've included a link to a handy resource in the instructor notes,
我在讲师说明中给出了一条链接
appropriately titled choosealicense.com to help you out with this.
choosealicense.com 能帮你处理这类问题
In the spirit of contribution, if you have a preferred way for others to
秉承开源精神 如果你有为你的项目做出
contribute to your project, the readme is the right place for that, too.
贡献的首选方法 请写到 readme 里
Briefly outlining simple steps, a style guide or
简述操作步骤 代码风格
whatever information you'd like others to know about contributing,
补充上希望贡献者了解的信息
is a great way to make your project more accessible for those wanting to help.
这能给他们带来很多便利
Some services, like ones that check to see if all your tests are passing,
有一些类似代码检查的服务
will provide special graphics, known as shields, for your readme's.
能为你的 readme 引入名为 shields 的特殊标记
These shields are useful because they're provided by a third party, and
这些工具由第三方提供
let your users know helpful information about your code.
帮助用户了解有关代码的信息
If this seems a bit confusing for now, don't worry too much about it.
如果你还不太明白 不要在意
I know when I started writing documentation these really confused me
我刚开始写文档也为此感到困惑
because I thought I needed to have them.
认为自己必须引入这种东西
Once you've written lots of tests in your code,
在你的代码包含了很多测试时
these shields will become useful.
shields 确实有所帮助
But when you're just getting started, don't worry too much about it.
但最开始的时候可以忽略它们
A word of caution, don't make your life more complicated than it needs to be.
记住 别让事情变得过于复杂
Allow your documentation to grow with the code base and
随着代码的增长去更新文档
only add new information as needed.
只在必要情况下向其中加入新的信息
We've looked at just a few potential sections you might want to include in
我们刚刚看过一些可以引入
your readme as you document your code but don't limit yourself to just these.
你的 readme 的文档内容 但不要局限于此
As your code base grows,
随着代码量的增加
which sections might also make sense to add to your readme?
哪些部分也适于加入 readme中 ?
Known bugs, frequently asked questions, press that your project has received,
已知 BUG  常见问题 你的项目已完成的报道评论
a table of contents or pictures of your cat.
内容列表或是你家猫咪的图片
Select as many as you think apply.
勾选所有你认为符合的选项